Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Manuscripts & Writings
  - Subseries B: Works by Others
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst, 1995-2001, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
      Smart Hearts in the City.
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Southern, Nile, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      "The Night the Bird Blew for Doctor Warner".
    - Southern, Terry, 1974, 1992, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
      "Heaven Can't Wait"; "Child Molester"; "The Secret Life of Larry Rivers"; "Slippery When Wet"; "Twice on Top"; "The Drift"; "The Refreshing Ambiguity of the Deja Vu"; "Origins of the Lampman".
    - Southern, Terry, 1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
      "Reflections on a Golden Heritage"; "Dynamite & Lemonade".
    - Southern, Terry, 1976, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
      "Little Mister"; "Johnny Stud"; "A Hustle Not Wholly Devoid of a Certain Grossness, Granted".
    - Southern, Terry, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
      The Donkey and the Darling.
    - Southern, Terry, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
      "Tough City".
    - Southern, Terry and Dick Fontaine, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      "D.J.".
    - Sparks, Esther, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Stubbs, Ann, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Towle, Tony, 1978, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Trantino, Thomas, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Tschechne, Martin, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      "Larry Rivers, the Last Hippie", in Art Magazine (Oct 1992).
    - [Unidentified Authors], 1984, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - [Unidentified Authors], 1991, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - [Unidentified Authors], undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - [Unidentified Authors], undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - [Unidentified Authors], undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
      "Working".
    - [Unidentified Authors], undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - [Unidentified Authors], undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - [Unidentified Authors], undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
      "The Free Way"; "Baba and Aquarius".
    - Various Poets, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
      Contains poems by various writers compiled together by Rivers.
    - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Wald, Eric, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      "Inside My Heart".
    - Waldman, Anne, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      "Riparian".
    - Weaver, William, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Weinstein, Arnold, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
      "Mahagonny".
    - Weinstein, Arnold, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Weinstein, Arnold, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
      "Presenting: The East Thirteenth Street Band!".
    - West, Marlowe Brien, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, Rob, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Wolf, Stephen, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Zeiger, L.L., undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Subseries C: Interviews conducted by Larry Rivers and Arnold Weinstein
    Subseries C contains typescripts of interviews of subjects other than Larry Rivers. Most of these were conducted by Rivers and Arnold Weinstein, as research for Rivers’ autobiography.
    Materials are arranged alphabetically by interview subject.
    - Blaine, Nell, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Burckhardt, Rudy, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Capp, Al, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Compiled Interviews, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
      Contains segments of interviews Rivers conducted in preparation for his autobiography, compiled for their relevance to one specific subejct.
    - Cooper, Arnold, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Freilicher, Jane, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Geldzahler, Henry, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Grossberg, Ben, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Grossberg, Sonya and Samuel, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Jeter, Al, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Kanovitz, Howard, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Koch, Kenneth, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Legere, Phoebe, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Maysles, Judy, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Rivers, Joseph, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Rivers, Steven, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Tabachnick, Ann, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified Subjects, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - WPA Project Transcripts, [1977] (Box 25, Folder 41)
      Related Archival Materials note
      Videos of Rivers's WPA interviews can be found in Series XVI: Video.
  - Subseries D: Interviews conducted by others
    Subseries D contains typescripts of interviews given by Rivers over the course of his career.
    Materials are arranged alphabetically by title, where available, or by interviewer in the case of untitled or unpublished interviews.
    - Barnett, Catherine, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      For New York Newsday.
    - Dellinger, Jade, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Diamondstein, Barbaralee, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Evans-Clark, Phillipe, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Hamptons Magazine, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Hunter, Sam, undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
      Contains 3 different interview manuscripts.
    - "The Juice and the Joy of It", 1994 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      Interview by Robert Enright, in Border Crossings 13:3.
    - "Larry Rivers and George Segal: Back in the USSR", 1977 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      Rivers interviewed along with George Segal, by Elizabeth Baker ( Art in America, Nov-Dec 1977).
    - Loria, Jeffrey, Jun 23 1978 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Lucie-Smith, Edward, undated (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Masters, Greg, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      For COVER magazine.
    - Pasti, Daniela, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      For La Repubblica.
    - Polgrean, Grace, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      For Cambio 16.
    - Sparks, Esther, Mar 21 1985 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Unidentified Interviewer, undated (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - "Why I Paint As I Do", 1959 (Box 25, Folder 58)
      Interview by Frank O'Hara, in Horizon 2:1.
- Series III: Photographic Material
  Series III: Photographic Material contains photographic prints, slides, contact sheets and negatives, divided into four subseries with respect to their original housing and arrangements.
  - Subseries A: Slide Cases
    Subseries A contains slides from numbered cases Rivers kept in his studio.
    Slides were transferred, in their original order, from slide cases to archival binders. Photocopies of original labels are included in each binder. Slide groupings and annotations are included in subject notes; notes added by the archivist are enclosed in square brackets.
    Separated Materials
    For reference, see "Source Slide Lists", Series (source), Box, Folder.
    - Slide Case 1, 1979-81, undated (Binder A1)
      Subjects include:
      Zihuatanejo, Sunsets.
    - Slide Case 2 (1 of 2), 1979-86, undated (Binder A1)
      Zihuatanejo.
    - Slide Case 2 (2 of 2), 1979-86, undated (Binder A2)
    - Slide Case 3, 1979-86, undated (Binder A2)
      Zihuatanejo, Coconuts Sign, Shots by Joe LoGiudice for At Z. Beach Painting - Not Used, Margo + Kids.
    - Slide Case 4, 1967-1968 (Binder A3)
      Africa: L.R.'s Trip w/Pierre Gaisseau & Gordon Parks Jr.
    - Slide Case 5, 1967-1968 (Binder A3)
      Africa '67-'68.
    - Slide Case 6, 1967-1968 (Binder A3)
      Africa '67 - '68, Contains 'Monuments & Leaders'.
    - Slide Case 7 (1 of 2), 1976-80 (Binder A4)
      Germany 1980, Fells Point, Baltimore, Caracas, Aspen, Russia, Baltimore.
    - Slide Case 7 (2 of 2), 1976-80 (Binder A5)
    - Slide Case 8, 1978-82, undated (Binder A5)
      London, Italy '82, France June `79, Rome, Catskill Yoga Retreat.
    - Slide Case 8, 1978-82, undated (Binder A6)
    - Slide Case 9 (1 of 2), 1974-84 (Binder A6)
      Paris (w/ Face in Forest), Southampton Thanksgiving (w/ Sheila at Wildlife Refuge), Florida (Mostly R.R. Station), 1974 Hirshhorn Trip, Phoenix 1983, Thanksgiving 1984 at 14th St., Germany '79-'80.
    - Slide Case 9 (2 of 2), 1974-84 (Binder A7)
    - Slide Case 10 (1 of 2), 1965-79, undated (Binder A7)
      City Junket, Black History...Other Artists' Works Within Rivers's Exhibition, Black History...Photos Used at Exhibition, Gloria de Duncan, Roy Lichtenstein, Claes Oldenburg, Jasper Johns, Jane Freilicher, Alex Katz, Robert Rauschenberg, Alan D'Arcangelo Shah-Nameh (Firdausi), Rainer Gross, Manfred Boecker, De Saint-Phalle &/or Jean Tinguely, Red Grooms, Balthus, Masson, Assorted Artists.
    - Slide Case 10 (1 of 2), 1965-79, undated (Binder A8)
    - Slide Case 11, 1982, 85-88 (Binder A8)
      Daria and Sam.
    - Slide Case 12, 1972 (Binder A9)
      Kenneth Koch & Larry Rivers: The Artist as Performed at Whitney Museum.
    - Slide Case 13 (1 of 2), 1972 (Binder A9)
      The Artist.
    - Slide Case 13 (2 of 2), 1972 (Binder A10)
    - Slide Case 14, undated (Binder A10)
      Mahagonny.
    - Slide Case 15, undated (Binder A10)
      "Forty Feet of Fashion".
    - Slide Case 16, 1977-87, undated (Binder A11)
      Summer in the Hamptons + Some Sam.
    - Slide Case 18 (1 of 2), 1963-88, undated (Binder A11)
      Larry Rivers, Picasso Sucks Shirt, Studio Scenes, L.R. at Work, Box 16: Exhibitions (Dwan '63, Horwitch '83, Simms '87).
    - Slide Case 18 (2 of 2), 1963-88, undated (Binder A12)
    - Slide Case 19, 1979, undated (Binder A12)
      Sheila Lanham, Confederate Flag.
    - Slide Case 20, 1979-81, undated (Binder A13)
      Regina, Gerry, Shelly (Exercise), Christopher Jason, Pierre Levai's Place, Johnny Carson Show: L.R., George Segal, Lorraine Dillon, Elle Faison, Diana, Larry, Michel: For 'Video Features' Card, Dara & Bucko, Kevin & Don, Susan Et Niki, T.O., Florence, Dave Levy, Lauren Olitsky, L.R. Signing 'Madame Butterfly'.
    - Slide Case 21 (1 of 2), 1978-83, undated (Binder A13)
      Black Teenagers, Tina L'Hotsky, Emma & Emily, Tucker Johnson, Niki - California, Steven's Birthday - Halloween Party, Steve & Muney Wedding in Z., Steve & Muney - Party at Clarice's, Joe, Mira - Stephanie's Birthday Party '82, Daria - Mixed, John Ashbery '82, Daria's Show, Emma's Play, Phoebe in Mexico.
    - Slide Case 21 (2 of 2), 1978-83, undated (Binder A14)
    - Slide Case 22, 1969-85, undated (Binder A14)
      Miscellaneous, 2 - Many Old Friends + Places, Clarice w/Gwynne as Infant, Parsons Student Works.
    - Slide Case 23, 1982-84, 88, undated (Binder A15)
      E. 13th St. Jazz Band, Including performance at the"Mudd Club, shots of members, i.e. Dave Levy, Phoebe Legere.
    - Slide Case 24, 1983-1988 (Binder A16)
      Loria Family, '85, '87, '88.
    - Slide Case 25, 1987-89, undated (Binder A16)
      [Rivers, his family and friends, and what appear to be source photographs for a portrait of the Worrel family].
    - Slide Case 26, undated (Binder A16)
      [Source photographs for a portrait commissioned by the Worrel family].
  - Subseries B: Photo Albums
    Subseries B comprises Larry Rivers and the Rivers Foundation's collection of photographs.
    Photographs were transferred, in their original order, from their original binders into archival binders. Photocopies of original labels are included in each binder. Expository notes have been added by the archivist with names of the binders' subjects. These notes are not comprehensive as to the contents of each binder and subjects contained therein.
    - Album 1: Early Family / The Bronx / Additional Family, 1935-78, undated (Binder B1)
      Larry Rivers, his close and extended family.
    - Album 1: Early Family / The Bronx / Additional Family, 1935-78, undated (Binder B2)
    - Album 2: Steven & Joseph, L.R. w/Both, all years / Augusta and Berdie / Steve & Joe with wives & children all years / Old Book #3 - Clarice / L.R. w/ Clarice, undated (Binder B2)
      Steven and Joseph Rivers.
    - Album 2 (cont'd): Steven & Joseph, L.R. w/Both, all years/ Augusta and Berdie/ Steve & Joe with wives & children all years/ Old Book #3 - Clarice/ L.R. w/Clarice, 1959-91, undated (Binder B3)
      Larry Rivers with Steven and Joseph, Augusta & Berdie / Steve & Joe / Wives & Children All Years.
    - Album 3: Clarice; L.R. w/ Clarice, undated (Binder B3)
    - Album 3: Clarice; L.R. w/ Clarice, undated (Binder B4)
    - Album 6: L.R. w/ Daria & Sam, All Years, 1986-93, undated (Binder B4)
      Daria Deshuk, Sam Deshuk Rivers, Larry Rivers, John Duyck.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Some negative film included.
    - Album 6: L.R. w/ Daria & Sam, All Years, 1986-93, undated (Binder B5)
    - Album 6 (cont'd): Friends Categorized Individually A - N, 1943-88, undated (Binder B5)
      John Ashbery, Francis Bacon, Joseph Beuys, Leonard Bernstein, Ted Berrigan, Nell Blaine, Rudy Burckhardt, Tibor de Nagy, Robert de Niro, Ahmet Ertegun, Lukas Foss, Jane Freilicher, Grace Hartigan, Clement Greenberg, Tom Hess, Abbie Hoffman.
    - Album 6 (cont'd): Friends Categorized Individually A - N, 1950-80, undated (Binder B6)
      Howard Kanovitz, Alex Katz, Franz Kline, Kenneth Koch, Joe LeSeuer, Al Leslie, Richard Lindner, Frank Lloyd, Norman Mailer, Marisol, Earl & Camilla McGrath, Joan Mitchell, Hans Namuth, David Hockney
    - Album 7: Friends Categorized Individually N - Z, 1950-77, undated (Binder B6)
      Niki de Saint-Phalle, Jean Tinguely, Frank O'Hara, Al Leslie, Ray Bremser, LeRoi Jones, Allen Ginsberg, Alex Lieberman, Robert Motherwell, Rene d'Harnoncourt, Nelson Rockefeller, George Plimpton, Robert Rauschenberg, Henry Geldzahler, Jimmy Schuyler
    - Album 7 (cont'd): Friends Categorized Individually N - Z, 1944-88, undated (Binder B7)
      Jimmy Schuyler, Walt Silver, Terry Southern, Debbie Harry, Virgil Thompson, Paul Taylor, Andy Warhol, Arnold Weinstein, Neil Welliver.
    - Album 7 (cont'd): Friends 1940s & 50s w/ Photos by Nell Blaine & Walt Silver, undated (Binder B7)
      Nell Blaine, John Ashbery, Cabell Brussel, Hyde Solomon, John Bernard Myers, Grace Hartigan, Jane Freilicher, Maxine Groffsky, Joe Hazan, Robert Rauschenberg, Tibor de Nagy, Sandra Lee, Robert Fizdale, Herbert Machiz, Gregory Corso, Jack Kerouac, Allen Ginsberg, Brendan Behan.
    - Album 7 (cont'd): Friends 1940s & 50s w/ Photos by Nell Blaine & Walt Silver, 1950-59, undated (Binder B8)
      Hans Hoffmann, Howard Kanovitz, [Mary Hoos], Jimmy Schuyler, Joe LeSeuer, Tibor de Nagy, Allen Ginsberg, Frank O'Hara, Harold Rosenberg, Irving Sandler, Grace Hartigan, Jane Freilicher, John Ashbery, Kenneth Koch, Al Leslie, Joan Mitchell, Mike Goldberg, Jean-Paul Riopelle.
    - Album 8: Friends 1960s Group Shots, 1950-68, undated (Binder B8)
      Howard Kanovitz, Jean Tinguely, Niki de Saint-Phalle, Clarice Rivers, Nell Blaine, LeRoi Jones, Hettie Jones, Donald Wessberger, Yves Klein, Rotraut Klein-Moquay, Frank O'Hara, John Bernard Myers, Frank Bowling, Joe LeSeuer, Willem de Kooning, Emmett Gragghin, Carol Selle.
    - Album 8 (cont'd): Friends 1960s Group Shots, undated (Binder B9)
      Joe LeSeuer, Elaine de Kooning, Clarice Rivers, Steven Rivers, Frank O'Hara, Joseph Rivers, Karl Flinker, Jane Wilson, Gerard Malanga.
    - Album 8 (cont'd): Friends 1970s Group Shots & those not in individual category, undated (Binder B9)
      Howard Kanovitz, Frank Bowling, Terry Southern, Diane Molinari, Don Schrader, Sylvia Miles, Charles Rydell, Gail Gerber, Taylor Mead, Robert Fraser, Ruth Kligman, Abbie Hoffman.
    - Album 8 (cont'd): Friends 1970s Group Shots & those not in individual category, 1970-87, undated (Binder B10)
      Diane Costello, Lori Stein, Evelyn Kuhn, Rainer Gross, Barbara Allen, Delphina Ratazi, Maurice Grosman, Michel Auder, Katie Casey, Bloum Condominas, Clarice Rivers, Diana Molinari, Steven Rivers, Jean Tinguely, Alexandra Auder, Lance Gumbs.
    - Album 8 (cont'd): Friends 1970s Group Shots & those not in individual category, 1979, undated (Binder B11)
      Nathan Joseph, Rainer Gross, Sheila Lanham, Mick Jagger, Eleanor Bingham, Rowland Miller.
    - Album 9: Friends 1980s and 90s, 1970-93, undated (Binder B11)
      Joe & Olga Hirshhorn, Jeff & Sivia Loria, Arnold Cooper, Charlotte Ambrose, Rainer Gross, Ernest Clay, Louie Crew, John Duyck, David Joel, Barbara Probst Solomon, Paula Abdul, Emilio Estevez.
    - Album 9 (cont'd): Climax Band, East 13th St., Band & Phoebe Legere, 1992, undated (Binder B11)
      The East Thirteenth Street Band, The Climax Band, Sam Rivers, Arnold Weinstein.
    - Album 9 (cont'd): Climax Band, East 13th St., Band & Phoebe Legere, 1981-93, undated (Binder B12)
      The East Thirteenth Street Band, The Climax Band, Red Mitchell, Pete Calandra, Howard Brofsky, Phoebe Legere, Howard Kanovitz, David Levy.
    - Album 9 (cont'd): Climax Band, East 13th St., Band & Phoebe Legere, 1985-98, undated (Binder B13)
      Phoebe Legere, Gwynne Rivers, Howard Brofsky, Sam Deshuk Rivers, Howard Brofsky, the Climax Band, Pete Calandra.
    - Album 9 (cont'd): Early Bands & Various Shots of L.R. on Sax, 1942-63, undated (Binder B13)
      [Primarily shots of Rivers playing his saxophone in the 1940s, 50s and 60s. Other subjects include Sherad Smith and Howard Kanovitz].
    - Album 10: Exhibitions, Openings & Special Events, 1956-81, undated (Binder B14)
      Helen Frankenthaler, Thomas and Audrey Hess, Clarice Rivers, Niki de Saint-Phalle, Jean Tinguely, Howard Kanovitz, Sam Hunter, Joe Hirshhorn.
    - Album 10 (cont'd): Exhibitions, Openings & Special Events, 1963-92, undated (Binder B15)
      Joseph Rivers, Clarice Rivers, Joseph Hirshhorn, Arnold Weinstein, Howard Brofsky, Howard Kanovitz, Jenny Holzer, Irving Sandler, Philip Pearlstein, Eric Fischl.
    - Album 10 (cont'd): Exhibitions, Openings & Special Events, 1963-92, undated (Binder B16)
    - Album 11: Theater, Film Collaborations, 1959-77, undated (Binder B16)
      Martin Sheen, Howard Kanovitz, John Ashbery, Jane Freilicher, Anne Aikinan, Allen Ginsberg, Tony Towle, Tatyana Grosman, Clarice Rivers, Kenneth Koch.
    - Album 11 (cont'd): Theater, Film Collaborations, 1951-86, undated (Binder B17)
      Clarice Rivers, Kenneth Koch, Fairfield Porter, Frank O'Hara.
    - Album 11: Work by other artists all years, undated (Binder B17)
      Christo, Franz Kline, Julian Beck, Henry Moore, Steven Antonakos, Lyman Kipp, Mario Garcia.
    - Album 11 (cont'd): Work by other artists all years, 1955-92, undated (Binder B18)
      Emma Rivers, Nigel Waymouth, Michel Auder, Jane Freilicher, Daria Deshuk.
    - Album 12: Mexico: Margo & the Kids, Africa (including Morocco), Russia, and various travels, 1964-81, undated (Binder B18)
      Garland Jeffries, Sheila Lanham, Elena Sisto, John Duyck, Margo & Chelan Chipman, Jane Freilicher, Joe Hazan, John Ashbery, Clarice Rivers.
    - Album 12 (cont'd): Mexico: Margo & the Kids, Africa (including Morocco), Russia, and various travels, 1941-76, undated (Binder B19)
      Clarice Rivers, Jane Freilicher, John Ashbery.
    - Album 12: LR Early, with Photos by Hans Namuth, Army Photos, Photos of Paris (Binder B19)
      Larry Rivers.
    - Album 13: L.R. 1960's, 1960-69, undated (Binder B20)
      Photographers include:
      Kathryn Abbe, Jay Good, Shunk Kender, Basil Langton, Look Magazine, Camilla McGrath, Peter Moore, John Reed, Tony Rodgers, Charles Rotmil, Walt Silver.
      Larry Rivers, Jill Johnson, Earl McGrath, Jean Tinguely, Clarice Rivers, Susan Lloyd.
    - Album 13: L.R. 1960's, 1960-69, undated (Binder B21)
    - Album 13: L.R. 1960's, 1960-69, undated (Binder B22)
    - Album 14: L.R. 1970s, 1971-91, undated (Binder B22)
      Dorothy Beskind, Nancy Compton, C. Brownie Harris, Sheila Lanham, Camilla McGrath, Diana Molinari.
    - Album 14 (cont'd): L.R. 1970s, 1970-79, undated (Binder B23)
      Includes a note from Lisl Steiner.
    - Album 14: L.R. 1980s & 90s, 1980-97, undated (Binder B23)
      Martin Brett Axon, Lucien Clergue, Allen Ginsberg, Camilla McGrath, Lenore Sakora, Yoshihiko Veder, Robert Mates, Sanjiro Minamikawa, Sebastian Piras.
    - Album 14 (cont'd): L.R. 1980s & 90s, 1982-97, undated (Binder B24)
      Arnold Weinstein, David Joel, Aldon James, John Duyck.
  - Subseries C: Inventory and Source Material Binders
    Subseries C contains the remaining photo binders in the collection, which comprise inventory and source material catalogs.
    Items were transferred, in their original order, from their original binders into archival binders. Photocopies of original labels are included in each binder, where present. Expository notes have been added by the archivist with names of the binders' subjects. These notes are not comprehensive as to the contents of each binder and sbujects contained therein. Any notations or titles created by the archivist are enclosed in square brackets.
    - Inventory Binder, 1951-1990 (Binder C1)
    - Inventory Binder, 1994-1996 (Binder C2)
    - Inventory Binder (1 of 2), 1994-1997 (Binder C2)
    - Inventory Binder (2 of 2), 1994-1997 (Binder C3)
    - Inventory Binder (1 of 6), 1997-2000, undated (Binder C3)
    - Inventory Binder (2 of 6), 1997-2000, undated (Binder C4)
    - Inventory Binder (3 of 6), 1997-2000, undated (Binder C5)
    - Inventory Binder (4 of 6), 1997-2000, undated (Binder C6)
    - Inventory Binder (5 of 6), 1997-2000, undated (Binder C7)
    - Inventory Binder (6 of 6), 1997-2000, undated (Binder C8)
    - Inventory Binder, undated (Binder C8)
    - Price Info L. Rivers (1 of 2), undated (Binder C9)
    - Price Info L. Rivers (2 of 2), undated (Binder C10)
    - Print Retrospective, Gallery Version (1 of 2), undated (Binder C10-C11)
    - Print Retrospective, Gallery Version (2 of 2), undated (Binder C11)
    - Print Retrospective, Museum Version (1 of 2), undated (Binder C11-C12)
    - Print Retrospective, Museum Version (2 of 2), undated (Binder C12)
    - Print Show, 1991-1992 (Binder C12)
    - Some Portraits by Larry Rivers, & Some Photographs Used In the Creation Thereof, undated (Binder C12)
    - Source Material Vol I, 1978-85, undated (Binder C13)
      People - Friends of Larry Rivers, Also - Source Material Related to Portrait Commissions i.e. Michel de Gréce, Source Material for 'Roots' Painting.
    - Source Material Vol Ia, 1974-80, undated (Binder C14)
      Johnson family, David & Judy Maysles, Al Capp, Peter & Ursula, Totah, Milano, Sheila Lanham and Gwynne and Emma Rivers.
    - Source Material Vol Ib, 1973-89, undated (Binder C15)
      Joe & Olga Hirshhorn, Lincoln, Rivers's parents and ancestors, Carly Simon, Casey Lee, Dick Cavett, Roy and Dorothy Lichtenstein.
    - Source Material Vol Ic, 1979, 87, undated (Binder C16)
      Christophe de Menil, Diana Molinari, Jim Carroll, Tony Towle, Quina Fonseca, Frank and Susan Lloyd, Dorothy Beskind, and the Bob Miller family.
    - Source Material Vol Id (1 of 2), 1975-82, undated (Binder C16)
      More friends of L.R.; other people; portraits with related source; 'human' source.
    - Source Material Vol Id (2 of 2), 1975-82, undated (Binder C17)
    - Source Material Vol Ie, 1982-83, undated (Binder C17)
      Ahmet Ertegun, Delphina, Carinthia, Julia Robinson, David Diamond, Abe List, and Allie Kaiser, as well as some stills from the shooting of At Z. Beach.
    - Source Material Vol If (1 of 2), 1970-85, undated (Binder C18)
      Henry Geldzahler, Tatyana Grosman, Jean Tinguely, Niki de Saint-Phalle, Larry Rivers, Sheila Lanham, T.T. Hudson, Irving Luntz, Carol Selle, Walter Feildshenfeldt, Gloria Luria, Zack Zucker, Barbara Allen, Joe LoGiudice, Patsy Cummings and Evelyn Kuhn.
    - Source Material Vol If (2 of 2), 1970-85, undated (Binder C19)
    - Source Material Vol Ig (1 of 2), 1980-88, undated (Binder C19)
      Joy Haft, Herr Dobler, Herr Becker, Tonninelli, Marc (Michele R's friend), Pierre and Paula Levai, Don Schrader, and Daria Deshuk.
    - Source Material Vol Ig (2 of 2), 1980-88, undated (Binder C20)
    - Source Material Vol Ih (1 of 2), 1980-85, undated (Binder C20)